[
    {
        "front": "てんきよほう",
        "back": "weather forecast",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいふう",
        "back": "typhoon",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちかづく",
        "back": "to approach",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちほう",
        "back": "region",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "なんせい",
        "back": "south-west",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "くも",
        "back": "cloud",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "サイン",
        "back": "sign",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふえる",
        "back": "to increase",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "へる",
        "back": "to decrease",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうい（する）",
        "back": "care/ to be careful",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひがし",
        "back": "east",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほくどう",
        "back": "north-east",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "きた",
        "back": "north",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほくせい",
        "back": "north-west",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "にし",
        "back": "west",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "なんせい",
        "back": "south-west",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "みなみ",
        "back": "south",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    },
    {
        "front": "なんとう",
        "back": "south-east",
        "chapter": "N4 C26"
    }
]